So this way I will not have
the handcuffs and stand like this in
underwear It's not happening So then I drive
rather blindfolded and completely unaware
about what happens Help Measured hand grinder
Hey dude Okay No hell Like
get everyone and don't get nervous Yes but that
helps a lot, but I'm sitting
and start stuttering a little when I get up
nervous Yes, it can be so sexy and
sit here and stutter maybe I can say
friend too Love her very much
but like this Yes but she is like this no
I'm like this We go to the pub. We
fix something on the pub (or in the last minute) like Bar no
but Eppa you can't just go and ask
if you are allowed to enter the pub like Mm Fast
I just but yeah Who cares what If they
[Music]
the evening Lazaro and
Elina you were touched and John and Ebba
and had to leave your couple the same evening Vi
will start with You can come up
and should ask me